Oh my, that looks quite good on you.
In all my years, I've never received
such a strange request for clothing.
But the pleasure was mine, sir.
Here, I gotta go.
Keep the change. See ya.
Uh, thank you, sir.
Let go!
Let go of me!
And don't you dare touch me there,
you - Hey, don't say it like that!
No, I don't wanna!
I wanna keep going with you guys!
Listen, little miss.
We're not vacationing here.
My daughter Jotaro's mother is
in grave danger at the moment.
We're on this journey to save my
daughter's life, not to put yours at risk.
Forget this running away
business and start heading home.
I'm sure your parents are worried
sick, wondering where you are.
There.
Fine.
I suppose so.
I'll make you look good
this time, Grandpa.
Hmm?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
See ya!
Life is just a bunch of goodbyes anyway!
I do sort of wish I could have seen
him once more before I had to go.
Goodbye! Jojo!
You better save your mom!
We're all counting on you!
I'll be cheering you on!
Let's go.
I'll see you
next time.
Koubushi kanatsu Zainar
with Vision Star and Cloud
Pakistan is a young country?
established in 1947 following
its separation from India.
But when Japan was still
a hunter-gatherer culture,
Pakistan was the seat of a
highly developed civilization.
Here in Pakistan,
the people carry on the 5,000-year
history of the Indian subcontinent.
I gotta say, Jotaro,
I'm impressed you got a Japanese
school uniform made here in Pakistan.
The fit is perfect, too.
It's 100 % wool.
Hey, Polnareff, are you
okay driving right now?
The fog in this area
is getting quite thick.
These aren't exactly
the safest conditions.
It's one hell of a drop off the right
side, and there's no guardrail anywhere.
Hmm, the fog looks even thicker up ahead.
It's not even three o 'clock
yet, but we should head in.
Let's find a place to stay
in that town for the night.
Do you think they have nice hotels?
Nice hotel, huh?
That's right, and it better
have a decent bathroom.
I...
I just couldn't get used
to the really strange
toilets they have all over
India and the Middle East.
What the hell?
Was that a dead dog?
What's the matter, Jotaro?
Oh, uh, it was nothing.
Hmm?
Hey this is a nice little town don't
you think there must be at least a few
Thousand people living here let's ask
about a hotel at that restaurant over
There but there's a weird quiet about
this place no matter where we've gone
Every other place has been rowdy and
congested it's probably because of the Fog.
Listen up, guys.
In Pakistan and the rest of the Islamic
world, this is how you greet people.
First, you smile and
say, As-Salaam-Alay-Koom.
Uh, no harm intended.
No need to close up shop just for us, sir.
We just wanted to ask a question.
Are there any hotels here in town?
Anybody home?
I do not know.
Good day. Hey, wait a minute!
What do you mean you don't know?
Huh what's with that
guy that can't be right
i must have imagined
it i'm sure he couldn't
understand you because
your pronunciation's
so bad let's just go
ask that guy over there
excuse me sorry but we're
looking for a hotel around
here preferably a hotel
with nice clean bathrooms.
Do you know any of that?
Whoa! Hey you! What's wrong?
What the hell?
He's dead!
With that look of fear on his face!
What's going on?
Why is he lying dead in the road?
What could have killed him?
A heart attack?
A stroke it's possible but look what
we've got here is no ordinary heart
Failure it's a gun wait a minute this
guy's holding a gun you just noticed Check
it out it's still smoking he must have
just fired it maybe two to five Minutes
ago either way he must have died
right before we arrived in town do you?
Do you think he shot himself?
No, I doubt it.
His body doesn't seem to have any visible
wounds, and there's no blood anywhere.
Then how'd this guy die?
This isn't natural!
Look at him!
His face is all twisted, like
he was screaming another terror!
Astounding.
You gotta wonder who or what
he shot at with that gun.
What exactly happened?
Didn't anyone here see anything?
No one stopped to help!
Excuse me! Ma 'am, wait!
Someone has died here!
Please call the police!
Pardon me, young man.
My boils seem to be festering today.
My apologies.
You had a question.
What was it that you needed?
I asked if you could please
call the police, ma 'am.
The police?
What would I do that for?
Look, that man's dead.
Someone is dead, you say?
How terribly unfortunate.
I'm not sure if there is
anything I can do about that.
I already asked you to
call the police twice.
Of course, call the police.
I think you did say that.
Well, good day, sir.
My boils are infected.
They are so itchy, so terribly itchy.
What is with the people in this town?
There's a man lying dead in the street,
and nobody seems even the
slightest bit concerned.
Didn't they hear the gunshot?
Nobody's doing anything.
It's like they don't even care.
These people are more oblivious than
the most jaded New Yorker or Tokyoite.
The dark.
This blasted fog just keeps
getting thicker and thicker.
It's almost as if the fog is
swallowing the town whole.
This is really creepy.
Call me crazy, but doesn't that
part there look like a skull?
What do you want to do you don't think it
could be the work of
another stand user do you?
Probably not there's no motive
why would someone who's after us
kill a man who has nothing to do
with us before we even got here?
there's no reason for a stan user
to kill him who knows the way he
died is obviously unnatural let's
examine the body before the police
come just try not to touch it
right this might be something it
appears he was traveling too just
like us he has bus and train tickets
in his pocket and he looks like
he might be indian he's carrying
indian money on him i'm guessing
he's not from this town oh look at
this wound he's got a gaping hole
here right in his upper chest
this must be what killed him hang
on why isn't there any blood coming
out with a fatal chest wound this
big there should be blood gushing
everywhere unless of course this
is no ordinary murder looks like
things are about to get messy
we've got to get to the bottom of
this it's time to search him take
off his clothes what happened to
his body there are tons of holes
all over this guy he's like that
cartoon cheese you see on tom and
jerry and there's not a drop of
blood anywhere near those wounds
how on earth was this man killed
what does all of this mean be careful
there wasn't a stand user here?
You can bet there's one here now.
Everyone, get in the car!
We're leaving this town now! Ah!
What the...
Impossible!
This isn't the car!
No! No!
Ah!
Hermit! Purple!
Hey, old man, what in
the hell are you doing?
You're crazy.
Huh? Oh, no!
What do you mean, what am I doing?
The car was right here just a minute ago!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
We just parked the car
over there and walked.
What?
But just now I could
have sworn that... Ugh!
Well, hello, good sirs.
I see you are travelers.
I'm afraid with this fog, it's
dangerous to leave the town now.
There are many cliffs, you know.
I run my own bed and
breakfast not far from here.
If you'd like, why not
stay there for the night?
There's plenty of room for everyone.
I'll even give you a healthy discount.
Finally!
We've actually met a
normal person for once.
We have to assume a stand user
is hiding somewhere in this town.
With this fog, there's no
telling what our enemy could do.
They could be next to
us, and we wouldn't know.
We absolutely cannot let
our guard down tonight.
You know, guys, I realize no
one's attacked us quite yet,
but damn, this town is creepy.
Come on.
This way, Master Joestar.
That building over there
is my bed and breakfast.
Follow me, and I'll
show you to your rooms.
Try not to fall behind.
I know it doesn't look like
much, but it has history.
About 20 years ago, one of the
007 movies was filmed here.
And when John Lennon of the
Beatles visited the country,
he spent the entire time in our
little hotel. What? Seriously? Oh, no.
I was just pulling your leg, young man.
What?
Still, it is quite a lovely hotel.
I've put my heart and soul into it.
We don't have any other guests at the
moment, so you can pick the dinner menu.
Would you prefer meat?
If not, we have fresh fish available.
Wait a second, Grandma.
Ma, before, you called
me Joestar, didn't you?
How did you know my name?
Come now, that delightful
young man next to you said Mr.
Joestar earlier.
I may be old, but my ears still work.
You mean me?
I think I said it, but I'm not sure.
Ah, you did, sir.
When you've been working in this
business for as many years as I have?
you really learned to memorize
people's names quickly.
So I'm sure of it.
By the way, ma 'am, I
just noticed the bandages.
What happened to your hand?
Oh, this?
A minor burn, nothing more.
I suppose it's just my old age, but I
accidentally spilled boiling water on it.
Oh, don't be silly, madame.
You hardly look a day over 40,
and that's God's honest truth.
What do you say you
and I get dinner alone?
Oh, you naughty boy.
Don't tease an old woman like that.
You damn babbling, pathetic fool.
It is you I despise most, Polnareff.
I'll make you suffer a pain 1,000
times worse than what my son endured.
Then I'll cut off your dick and rip
out your guts to finish you off.
Oh!
This doesn't look bad at all!
Here, Kakyoin. Right.
My autograph's worth as much as Lennon's.
Here.
I'm Paul Nareff, after all.
Make sure you take care of it.
Of course.
I'll make sure it's
preserved for all time.
To commemorate the day I murder you.
It's done.
Well then, allow me to show
you to your rooms, gentlemen.
Oh man, talk about a weird town.
Now time to hit the loo!
I don't think it's functional.
Oh, if that's the case,
I won't be able to use Hermit
Purple to get info on the enemy.
Hey, Mr.
Joestar, what's the looks like?
My room doesn't have a bathroom.
Is there one in here I can use?
Perhaps the bathroom here is communal.
Ah, of course.
He's so carefree.
Good grief!
A stand user could attack at any moment.
He should be on guard.
So, the Joestar party
is on the third floor.
Maybe me and my six-shooter
ought to pay them a visit.
Ah, Hall Force.
So you've come. That's right.
I finally managed to track those sorry
bastards as far as this creepy town.
But finding you is surprising, Yabba.
I didn't think you'd come all
the way out here yourself.
What's the matter, Nyabba?
Did I say something wrong?
Forgive me.
I'm just happy, whole horse.
It means so much that you're here.
Thank you for coming to
see this lonely old woman.
It is so wonderful to finally see you.
Tell me something.
You and my son were friends,
were you not, Cold Horse?
Were we friends?
Uh, well, I...
Yes, we're thick as thieves, ma 'am.
So you were close?
Yeah, we were practically brothers.
He was a dear friend and
an excellent partner.
What's this all about?
You aren't acting like
yourself at all in Yoma.
His death must weigh heavily on you.
Will you avenge him?
Is that why you're here?
Yes, that's exactly it.
I'm gonna make sure those bastards
pay for killing my best friend.
That's exactly what I want to hear!
Because now I can kill you
too, you filthy traitor!
Yoma, what the hell are you doing?
Idiot, isn't it obvious?
You abandoned him to save yourself.
I swore I would kill you
the moment I saw you again.
You deserve the same as the Joestars.
How dare you call yourself his
best friend, cretin, Judas?
Wait, you got it all wrong.
By the time I got there, Sinnerfall
was already a goner, honest.
You wretch, you're as unforgivable
as that bastard Polnareff.
I'll have you die at the
hands of my stand, Justice.
Wait, have mercy.
Only a few have seen the
terrifying power of my stand.
And now you will join all of
them in death, whole horse.
Huh?
What the hell is happening
to the blood of my arm?
It's like it's all just evaporating.
It made such a fine wound, did it not?
That's right, this is justice,
a stand that's made of fog.
Any wound my stand happens to graze,
becomes a gaming hole, and then...
Justice wants to dance, whole horse.
My stance fog has entered
your arm like a string,
and now you're a helpless puppet
I can do with as I please.
You will die by your
own hand, whole horse!
Damn it!
You shouldn't get so damn cocky! Emperor!
Die, you crazy old hag!
Justice prevails.
Huh?
What the hell was that noise?
Sounded like a giant explosion.
It came from the room at the
back of the downstairs lobby.
Is something wrong Polnareff huh?
We heard something strange
and came to investigate.
Same here.
I was about to check downstairs.
I'll look in the lobby first.
Call me if you find anything!
Okay.
Your time's finally come, Ponareth.
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If you move too quick.
They're falling down like a domino.
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They've got the money on a bed.
Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Foreign types with a hookah. I say.
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses take their trays.
Spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves, oh, hey-oh.
You drop your drink,
then they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings, they're
walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say.
Walk
like
an Egyptian.
He's in the bathroom, but he's
been in there for some time.
Of course he's taking a shit.
The bathroom is at the end of the hall.
I thought I just heard the word toilet.
What are you giggling about?
Why am I always getting
ambushed in bathrooms?